Welcome back to Cleveland Browns Daily
brought to you by Valley Beneficial
Sports Betting partner of your Cleveland
Browns. And this is folks a great
personal treat for me as we are welcomed
by one of the greatest professional
wrestlers of all time, Matt Hardy. You
know him as broken Matt Hardy, woken
Matt Hardy. Matt Hardy version one. And
of course, he is a multi-time 15
different this is according to
cagematch.net 15 different tag titles
held with his brother throughout his
career. Multiple single titles. It's
just an honor to talk with you, an honor
to be with you. And thanks so much for
taking the time today.
>> Uh thanks for having me, man. Yeah, 15
uh major ones I think is is what they
are counting it at right now. Uh we've
had about uh we've had four almost
almost 50. We've had 47 all together.
Different
>> 47 Well, when you go on an expedition
for gold, you're going to you're going
to collect quite a bit.
>> And we love to do it. We can't do it
enough.
>> Exactly. All right. Coming up this
Saturday right here in Cleveland, April
11th at the Wolstein Center, it's TNA
Rebellion. You and your brother Jeff
will be defending the tag team titles,
TNA tag team titles against
people who quite frankly you've had some
runins with in the past in terms of
you're looking talking Brian Meyers and
and Bear Bronson, but against the
system. How much you looking forward to
that one and obviously walking in as
champions, but more importantly walking
out still the TNA tag team champions.
>> Uh very excited for it. I mean uh
Cleveland is an amazing wrestling city.
Uh for people that don't know, Cleveland
is uh is where myself and Jeff, we got
put on the map. That is where
>> I was supposed to lead with that.
>> Well, that that is where the
>> October 17th, 1999, No Mercy. That's
right.
>> Yeah. 1999 No Mercy. And that that match
changed everything for us. We went from
being WWE wrestlers to WWE superstars.
That was the night. Also, it's a very
fond memory for me. I won the first ever
uh scramble match for the ECW World
Championship there in Cleveland as well.
So, Cleveland has been a good city to me
and I'm hoping it is good to me this
Saturday as we are facing a very tough
team. Brian Meyer is extremely talented.
Bear Bronson is a newcomer. He is the
wild card. He is very unknown, but he is
a very, very dangerous man. And I think
the system is more dangerous now than
they ever been.
>> And they've won, they've twotime tag
team champions, the system. They're
different members obviously along with
Brian Myers there. But how have you and
your brother Jeff, what keeps you going?
I mean, you have what one of the great
careers in the history of this business?
You've been doing it as I mentioned from
the trampolines in the 80s in Cameron,
North Carolina. Start Omega. Then by 99
you're in the WWE and you just mentioned
it October 17th right here in Cleveland.
Changes everything. You were the new
brood then, not even the Hardy Boys at
that time. And here we are. It's 2026,
brother. You go through and you look at
the body of work that you guys have put
together, not only from a creative
standpoint, but from the physicality and
what you've literally put your bodies
through. What keeps you doing this here
in the year 2026? not only doing it,
doing it at the highest of levels.
>> Uh I I just think more than anything, it
is our passion for pro wrestling as
children and as kids. Once pro wrestling
got a hold of us, uh we loved it so much
and it became our dream and we were both
uh obsessed with becoming pro wrestlers
because we thought it was like these
guys are living breathing superheroes.
You know, people who are doing stuff,
you're doing it live, there's sports,
there's drama, there's entertainment, a
little bit everything. And internally,
you know, sure, we're 51 and 48, but
internally we feel like we're 21 and 18.
And I think that's what keeps us going.
It it is our passion for pro wrestling.
And some people would say it is a
uncommon passion. Uh, as that Omega DVD
said, you know, because we have we've
taken a lot of bumps off our bum card,
but I would just say it is passion and
love for the business.
>> You have to have it, right? I mean,
there's no other way that you could do
what it is that you're doing. And I've
been lucky enough to befriend, you know,
some people in in your line of work.
Matt Cardona, Dolph Ziggler, The Miz.
Uh, and many of you have the same story.
This was our dream. This is something we
were hooked on as as kids. And now you
get to live it. And I will tell you
this, I've been to a lot of great
wrestling events. I've been to a lot of
Wrestlemania. I've had the opportunity
to be front row for a lot of them. In
fact, when and I know that I don't know
how this match sits with you
historically, Wrestlemania 25, brother
versus brother. I was there in second
row when Jeff hits Swanon throws a shirt
in the crowd. That's in my house, his
his tank top. You guys have had so many
big moments, but I, like I said, I've
been to a lot. When you guys came back
and I want to say it's Wrestlemania 33,
is that did I get that right?
>> Orlando, Florida.
>> 17. Yes.
>> So, your tag title match was going to be
it was a latter match, a surprise.
Obviously, you guys come back. The next
match was going to be Miz. Shane
McMahon, and I was there with with the
Miz, and so we got brought down. We're
down like on the going to be ready to be
moved into the front on the camera side
for his match.
We obviously nobody had any idea when
your guys music hit and we're walking.
We're on the floor now of the arena of
the stadium, the football stadium down
there in Orlando, the Citrus Bowl.
>> It shook. The ground shook. Was that one
of, from your standpoint, one of the
greatest pops that you've ever been a
part? I think it's one of the greatest
pops in the history of wrestling,
period. But what was that moment like
for you guys through your eyes?
>> Absolutely. I mean, it it was so wild
because Jeff and I there was so much
secrecy around that, right? They did a
really good job of uh of not letting
that secret out. There were less than 10
people that really knew we were going to
be there, that we were ressigned and
everything else. And uh and we played
our part. We did everything that we
could to uh to keep things on the DL.
>> Yes, you did.
>> And uh and and we got there about an
hour before. They asked us to get
hoodies in Orlando in April, which was
kind of challenging. They ended up being
pink hoodies. If you ever seen the
documentary, that's pretty cool. Uh so
we sneak into the building, we get onto
a bus, uh we talk to the other couple
teams for just a few minutes about uh
the game plan of what we got going on.
And then once the first entrance goes
down and goes to the ring and say go and
then we ran from that bus and Gorilla
was up three flights of stairs, it was
three stairs. My wife was pregnant. She
was carrying our one-year-old, one and a
half yearear-old on her back. So she was
furious having me cursing me out in
Spanish was really good thing. Uh we got
up there and then immediately it was
just so overwhelming because there was,
you know, John Cena and Shawn Michaels
and Triple H and Miss McMahon and
everybody else and it's like this big
family reunion and then all of a sudden
the music is hitting and we're going and
when we're walking out we have no idea
what this venue looks like. We hadn't
seen it yet. We had done an autograph
signing for six hours that day and it
was
>> Oh, I remember that was the distraction.
Yeah. Yeah, that that was a distraction.
And I I taken a photo when our whole
family, House Hardy, flew in that I was
going to post saying, "Thank you for the
weekend. It was great." And I did post
that saying that we had already left.
>> And uh and then and then we walked out
and the crowd was so legitimately su uh
excited. And the thing that was so
surprising to me is that, you know, TNA
was a company that was on the verge of
going out of business and the the Broken
Universe stuff, Broken Mountain brother
Nero made it hot and we get we was sold
to Anthem, a new company, actually took
over and and it gave us a lifeline to a
degree and so many people, you know,
said, "Oh, Tina's dying." But, you know,
the whole delete delete delete. There
were
>> Oh, we're going to get there. I have
many questions. Don't worry, we're going
to get there. There were there were
50,000 people doing that in Wrestlemania
and they were just as emotionally uh
excited as they could possibly be and
and for us it was just exhilarating. It
was intoxicating. It usually in those
moments you're just so overwhelmed and
it but this felt like a dream. It felt
surreal. It feels like it's blurry
around the edges as I'm trying to, you
know, recall the the the memory because
it was just such an amazing moment and
and and the the energy was palpable in
that. And I I think the further we get
away from that moment, the the higher
and higher it claims uh higher and
higher it climbs as one of the greatest
moments in Hardy Boy history.
>> I think it's one of the greatest moments
in wrestling history. And I'm not I'm
not being facitious. I mean, I've been I
was at every Wrestlemania from 19
through and had, you know, fortunately
to be in good spot from 19 through I
missed 18, which would have been Hogan
Rock, which probably would be the one
thing that I think maybe be on a par,
but from 19 through 40.
>> Well, the first match you saw at
Wrestlemania was me versus Rey Mysterio
then. V1
Safe Coield. Absolutely. I remember
that. Absolutely. Shannon Moore, the the
Matitude follower. You do still detest
green beans and and mustard.
>> Well, mustard it just strongly disliked.
Detest proper word.
>> It is.
>> Fact, Matt is undefeated as a singles
competitor in Wrestlemania.
>> Undertaker can't say that,
>> right?
>> No, he can't. Not anymore.
>> I'm two and0, baby. I got this streak
when it comes to singles matches
>> about going back real quick to that man
when you come out. Are you Did Kofi
know?
>> Yes. The
>> Okay. Cuz their reaction was off the
charts.
>> But but those guys Kofi and those guys
they only knew they they smartened them
up like 20 minutes before.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> They knew they were going to be
announced but they were like whoa. I
mean they were it was still it was still
I feel like they had they had they
haven't seen us.
>> Uh and it was going to be a shocker and
surprise. So that their their emotion
and their reactions were very authentic
and and once again kudo uh kudos to Kofi
and uh Big E and Xavier because they
they really they help make that moment
even more special with their reactions.
>> Well, I think there's something special
about what one of the cool things about
the business that you're in and and the
fraternity that you're in that you know,
like I said, I've been able to observe
adjacently is like when you have that's
respect. That is the ultimate respect.
when you get guys out there marking out
for for you like that's the ultimate
sign of respect and I think that's so
cool and you guys have been so
influential like I Kofi Kingston there's
no doubt you guys influence Kofi
Kingston's career life trajectory all of
it you know that's to me that's what
that's what makes it right those are the
kind of moments you live for sure it is
and and sometimes you know people go
like do you guys ever look back and
think about how influential you are and
like we we talk now at at Comic-Cons and
appearances we do to so many fathers or
mothers and their children that are like
now both fans of the Hardies and and
they support the Hardy Boys and they
they're catching up on, you know, all of
our matches and our body of work and and
it's amazing. They like bond over it and
and the fact that we have become
generational talents. The fact that we
have worked with so many young tag teams
that said we you were my favorite tag
team. You inspired me to do this. I
wanted to do this because I saw you and
Jeff doing it and and we get to work
with them now. So, it's it's real cool,
man. I don't even think we we we don't
take the time to like look back, stop
and look back and go like we did all
this influentially. Uh because we we
still want to be living in the moment.
We want to be present in the moment and
still be as good as we can be every
single night. Uh and that's what we want
to do this weekend against the system
obviously.
>> Yeah. And you're going to keep those tag
titles. And one of the things that's
cool about this kind of TNA run that
you've been on is you mentioned you know
the ladder match obviously that was with
Edge and Christian. Then we go back to
obviously Wrestlemania 17. We think
about TLC 2 when that involved the
Dudley boys. for you guys to get to have
that kind of, you know, that's what's
one of the beautiful things about
wrestling is that sometimes you get an
opportunity to to close a book but have
the proper book end to get that match
with the Dudley's. It was for me
>> poetry, perfect cinema, everything you
could have wanted out of that for you
guys. What was that like to to to lock
up one more time with them? I
>> I mean it it was amazing. I am so so
proud of that match. Um, Devon had had
some very serious health issues and he
he worked extremely hard to overcome
them and get into the to the best shape
he could. He he worked hard to get
cleared and he did get cleared and you
know we went into that we went into that
match with two missions. One to have an
amazing match and show people that we
can still make magic happen together.
Totally. And we did that. and and the
other mission was to keep Devon safe and
healthy and and give him one last great
match to really book in his career much
like you said before. And uh we are so
proud of that match. I I I just watched
that match back yesterday actually
because they just recently released the
video. They put the full match out on
the TNA YouTube channel and if you
haven't seen it yet, go watch it. It's
great.
>> Do it. Yes. I urge everyone.
>> We did enough uh exciting crazy table
hotspots to make people think like,
"Wow, this is like them in 2000." But we
did great storytelling as well talking
about like you know the Dudley's Bubba
is looking at the very end like okay
well it's over for us now it's over for
me it's over for us and and the thing
that is super surprising about that
match nor Jeff nor I we knew that was
going to be Devon's last match we want
to get him through it we did not know
that they were both going to retire and
on top of that boots at the end of the
match that was an absolutely authentic
moment uh whenever you saw that
happening that was our emotion uh in
real time because we had no idea that
was happening
That's so cool. And you know, one of the
things that's amazing about it is it's
one thing to like, you know, to lay that
out to be like, "Okay, we're going to do
this and you didn't know they were going
to try at the end, but say, you know,
we're going to go one more time, but
then to actually be able to get through
and what you brought to light about
Devon, to get through it and execute
it." Like that's the that's the beauty
of it is that you guys had this vision
and then delivered it sounds like
against some odds. And that's the be
that's the beauty of pro wrestling.
That's the absolute beauty of what you
can do. I mean that that that is the
beauty of that is the beauty of the art
of pro wrestling, you know, because we
do control uh several different aspects
of the industry and and and there are
ways you can make things that seem
impossible happen and that is that is
beautiful. That's a beautiful thing
about pro wrestling.
>> There's no doubt about it. I I went to
get back this earlier, but you mentioned
the broken universe. So, I have a a
group of friends that we've all watched
wrestling for forever.
We could not have been bigger fans of
the broken universe. I remember when you
went on Jericho's podcast, you did a
talk as Jericho that was like 2 hours
where you went through the whole thing.
I was riveted. One year I was driving to
the NFL scouting combine which is from
Cleveland to Indie. It's about a four
and a half hour drive. I listened to it
there and back. That's how much I
enjoyed the podcast and the broken
universe and you know Scarsgard and
Vanguard one and just everything every
detail. How where do the world okay for
people who maybe don't know about it and
you should go seek out 2016 I want to
say if I if I have that right I think
it's in that in that era
to reinvent yourself that way it's kind
of you think of the great you know icons
whether Madonna you know just to
completely reinvent yourself and you
could had to have the most fun ever
doing it but how did you kind of work
that out how did you workshop the accent
which I think makes it on some level and
just have that unbelievable renaissance
to your career
Uh, well, the funny thing is I I've
always tried to keep my finger on the
pulse of pro wrestling, like where
what's going on? And and and we're at
that point where
the wrestlers are getting smaller, their
height's getting a little shorter. They
don't weigh quite as much. Wrestling is
kind of changing and and and matches are
more exciting. There's much more uh
acrobatics in it, you know, and we we
ushered some of that in obviously back
in the day when we first started doing
our things, you know. And so I was like,
well, this is what pro wrestling is and
where it's at right now. And work rate
is very high. These guys have to have
great matches. That's kind of like a
requirement. If you're having a match on
top of telling a story, you have to have
make it really action-packed and it has
to be good quality action. I was like,
what if I go in the opposite direction
of that and I try something that is a
throwback to the early 90s Papa Shango
or when Undertaker first started and he
was magical. What if I tried to create
this supernatural character that was
very unique? And my wife and I, we had
uh start we had binged True Blood over a
few and I I thought the whole vampire
concept was so cool. How you see Eric
Northman who was my favorite on there.
Uh he had lived for a thousand years and
you see all these different periods and
how his clothing changes and how his
hairstyles changed and everything else.
And it's like it would be so great if
you could portray some sort of character
like that. Obviously I can't be immortal
but what if I could say I am cognizant
of where my soul in my body has been. So
then that when the body became the
vessel the vessel became my essence and
uh the fact that you listened to that
talk as Jericho interview that is
delightful you know that you listen to
it over four hours
>> wonderful. I I I tried to look I tried
to look for words that were very uh
archaic and p and I tried to incorporate
those you know that way I could seem
like I am a soul that was from thousands
of years ago and that was kind of the
whole concept behind the broken man
hearty persona. Did you have any idea
that it was going to become the
phenomenon that it become? As you
mentioned, and we fast forward, you
know, kind of jumping around, but to
that wrestling, a football stadium is
chanting delete. You had not been on WWE
TV in years,
>> right? And and in the broken universe is
what brought us back to WWE.
>> 100%. It was the hottest thing in
wrestling.
>> You know, Vince said, "Why why are
people doing why why are FANS DOING
DELETE, DELETE, DELETE? WHAT IS THAT?"
And you know, someone said, "Well,
that's what the Hardies are doing. the
Hardies. They're, you know, they they
have these new broken characters and and
it's very popular, very hot right now
and it's viral online. He said, "Bring
them back. Bring them all back." There's
only two of us, fans. So,
>> that's what when you go into the lake of
reincarnation. I mean, you never know
what's going to happen, right? There are
there are more versions. You're right
about that. But it's it's crazy how the
Hardy compound became such a character
in the Broken Universe, you know, which
was so beloved and family, right? Senor
Benjamin was your father-in-law. No
doubt. Everybody. Yeah. And you know
Scarsgard. People love Scarsgard.
Vanguard.
>> Scarsard's the best.
>> When when Vanguard won when Vanguard one
uh got hurt and killed like people were
so sympathetic.
>> I did not like it. Yeah.
>> It was wild. Yeah. Um but man, it it was
it was the most fun. That year of doing
Broken Mount was the most fun I've ever
had in my entire career. And and just
the the the fact that I got to create
and think out of the box and do stuff
that was so different was so much fun.
And I'm so proud of it. And it was so
cool that we got to do a little bit of
it uh last year at NXT because we did a
really cool deal where Jeff and I got
beat up. We dipped into the lake of
reincarnation and did a big video, came
back as Broken Matt and Brother Nero.
Thursday night on Impact, you're going
to see a brutal tag team table match uh
between, you know, ourselves and the
Righteous. And and I think I figured out
finally what the Righteous's goal was. I
I think their gold is to bring out
Broken Matt and Brother Nero. And I
don't know, they
>> Be careful what you ask for. Yeah, be
very careful what you ask for because
that that that could be a decision they
are going to extremely regret. So, uh we
we're we're going to be battered and
beat up going into the ring with the
system, but we are the Hardies. You
know, we uh uh a new catchphrase that I
just said and and and Tommy Dreamer was
a big fan of it. You know, uh there's no
one that has hardyh hardy heart because
regardless of how bad you beat us down,
you know, we will not die. We have the
guts to just keep ticking, man.
>> I like that. I'm not going to repeat it,
but I like what you're saying right
there. Again, this is all going down
here at Cleveland. I mean, you get an
opportunity to see Living Legends still
at the top of their game, the Hardy Boys
against the system. TNA tag team titles
on the line. TNA Rebellion, Saturday,
April the 11th, 2026 at the Woolstein
Center. Tickets are on sale right now
through Ticketmaster. And Matt, I just I
want to leave you with this because I
could talk to you all day and I know you
are a very busy man. You got a lot going
on, but this is a great thrill for me.
I'll tell you this kind of leave you
when you talk about kind of the impact
you have. So my kids for a long time I
had my kids like pretty hard into
wrestling. Now they're in high school
and you know they've moved on to to
other things but we went to a bunch of
Royal Rumbles, Wrestlemania together. My
son had like all the figures, play all
the video games and everything.
>> There are four people four people and I
told them that I was doing this
interview and they both marked out huge.
They're like you're going to talk to the
Hardies. You're going to talk to Matt
Hardy. So you, Jeff, AJ Styles, and
Kofi, who was always so nice to them
when he they got a chance to meet him
backstage. Those are the four people
that they to this day like when that's
wrestling to them. The Hardy Boys, AJ
Styles and Kofi Kingston.
>> Outstand. A AJ and Kofi are both amazing
humans. Very good. Great, great, great,
great pick by your kids.
>> Yeah. Raising them right. Raising them
right. Exactly.
>> Well, Matt, thank you so much for the
time. Tear it up at Rebellion. Get
through that table match with these no
good doers. We don't like these people,
but if they get Brother Nero and Broken
Mad Bag, they're going to get what they
uh had what they had coming. But go
check them out. TNA Rebellion, Saturday,
April 11th, 2026, Wolf Team Center.
Again, you get your tickets at Ticket
Master. All right, I got to tell you, a
personal great thrill for me today. I
really appreciate the time and the
conversation.
>> Thank you. And I hope to see each and
every one of you in Cleveland. If not, I
may have to delete you.
>> It's perfect. We'll be back. More Browns
Daily right after